Paint is being poured onto the floor.
油漆正在倒在地板上。
The brushes are resting on the ladder.
刷子放在梯子上。
The worker is removing his gloves.
工人正在脫掉手套。
The workers are preparing to paint.
工人們正在準備油漆。
Will John replace the damaged garage door or remove it?
約翰會更換或拆除損壞的車庫門嗎？
The renovations started two days ago.
整修工作是在兩天前開始的。
I think he will have it repaired.
我想他會把它修好。
I will remove that for you later.
稍後我會為你刪除它。
You put the down payment on the house this week, right?
你這週就付了房子的首付，對吧？
Yes, the real estate agent is busy.
是的，房地產經紀人很忙。
No, the property value hasn't gone down.
不，房產價值並沒有下降。
Of course. I did it first thing on Monday.
當然。我周一做的第一件事就是這麼做。
Questions 53 to 55 refer to the following conversation.
問題53至55涉及以下對話。
Good morning, Rick. I was hoping you could help me out with a problem I'm having.
早安，瑞克。我希望你能幫助我解決我遇到的問題。
Of course. What do you need help with?
當然。您需要什麼幫助？
Well, I'm not sure if you've heard, but I just got promoted to regional manager for our processor manufacturing plant in Asia.
嗯，我不確定您是否聽說過，但我剛剛晉升為我們亞洲處理器製造工廠的區域經理。
Congratulations! That's fantastic news.
恭喜！這是個好消息。
Thank you. But it means I'm going to have to move there and, well, I'm having trouble finding a place.
謝謝。但這意味著我將不得不搬到那裡，而且我很難找到地方。
Then you've come to the right spot. I can definitely help you find a new apartment. What kind are you looking for?
那麼您就來對地方了。我絕對可以幫助您找到新公寓。您在尋找什麼類型的？
I don't need anything too spacious, so a studio apartment is fine. But I do need a kitchen and it needs to be furnished.
我不需要太寬敞的東西，所以單間公寓就可以了。但我確實需要一個廚房，而且需要配備家具。
Not a problem. Anything else?
不是問題。還要別的嗎？
If it could be a short drive from work and have at least one supermarket nearby, that would be great.
如果距離工作地點只有很短的車程，並且附近至少有一家超市，那就太好了。
And what kind of a budget are you looking at?
您正在考慮什麼樣的預算？
The company will cover half of the rent, so anything under $1200 is fine.
公司會承擔一半的租金，所以 1200 美元以下的都可以。
Great. I'll have a look and see what I can find.
偉大的。我會看一下，看看我能找到什麼。
What happened to the woman?
那個女人怎麼了？
She was let go from her job.
她被解雇了。
She received a pay raise.
她得到了加薪。
She opened a factory.
她開了一家工廠。
She was promoted.
她升職了。
What does the woman mention about her ideal apartment?
這位女士提到她理想的公寓是什麼？
It needs to include furniture.
它需要包括家具。
It needs a large space.
它需要一個大的空間。
It's better to be close to a park.
最好離公園近一點。
It's within walking distance.
步行即可到達。
What does the woman imply about the rent?
女人問房租這件事代表什麼？
She will only have to pay part of it.
她只需要支付一部分。
She will be paying it entirely herself.
她將完全自己支付費用。
The company will cover the rent completely.
公司將全額支付租金。
The rent should not be too high.
租金不應該太高。
All tenants are required to pay their monthly utilities on time while they remain as residents in this apartment complex.
所有租戶在作為該公寓大樓的居民期間都必須按時支付每月的水電費。
require
要求
requires
需要
is required
是必須的
are required
是必需的
The architect who is responsible for the design of the new building will be coming by to check on the progress of construction.
負責新大樓設計的建築師將會過來檢查施工進度。
which
哪個
who
世界衛生組織
when
什麼時候
what
什麼
For Rent
出租
Modern apartment available for rent, located just a few minutes from downtown.
現代公寓可供出租，距離市中心僅幾分鐘路程。
The apartment is spacious, with two bedrooms, a living room, a dining room, a kitchen, and two bathrooms.
公寓很寬敞，有兩間臥室、一間客廳、一間餐廳、一間廚房和兩間浴室。
The living room and dining room are fully furnished, and the kitchen has all the necessary appliances.
客廳和餐廳設施齊全，廚房擁有所有必要的用具。
Furnishings for the bedrooms are not provided. The apartment is only two years old and in excellent condition.
不提供臥室家具。公寓只有兩年的歷史，狀況良好。
Access to an elevator is included.
房價含電梯。
Several supermarkets, a department store, a laundromat, bus stops and a subway stop can all be found within walking distance.
數家超市、百貨公司、自助洗衣店、巴士站和地鐵站均位於步行範圍內。
Rent is $1500 a month, with two additional months' rent required as a deposit. The minimum renting time is one year, with longer options available.
租金為每月1500美元，另需支付兩個月的租金作為押金。最短租賃時間為一年，也有較長的選擇。
The deposit will be returned upon  completion of the rental agreement, minus the cost of any damage to the apartment.
租賃協議完成後，押金將在扣除公寓損壞費用後退還。
For more information, or to arrange a viewing, contact Roy at 555-4329.
如需更多資訊或安排觀看，請致電 555-4329 聯絡 Roy。
space
空間
spacious
寬敞
specific
具體的
spatial
空間的
Furnishings for the bedrooms are not provided.
不提供臥室家具。
Furniture in the living room is extra.
客廳裡的家具是額外收費的。
Use of the refrigerator is not allowed.
不允許使用冰箱。
Pets are only allowed to remain inside for short visits.
寵物只允許在室內短暫停留。
find
尋找
founding
創立
founded
成立
be found
被發現
in addition to
另外
upon
之上
due to
由於
when
什麼時候
Tom Bradley 14:00
湯姆布拉德利 14:00
Hi, Mr. Hart. I'm sending this message to let you know that the pipes in the bathroom of my apartment are leaking quite badly.
你好，哈特先生。我發送此訊息是為了讓您知道我公寓浴室的管道漏水嚴重。
Also, the noise from the construction site across the road is really loud and distracting.
此外，馬路對面建築工地的噪音非常大，令人分心。
These issues were not mentioned to me at the time of signing the lease.
在簽署租約時，我沒有提到這些問題。
Bill Hart 14:03
比爾·哈特 14:03
Tom, I'm sorry to hear about the problems with your apartment.
湯姆，得知你的公寓出現問題，我感到很遺憾。
I was unaware of the leaking problem. Don't worry though, your rental agreement states that the costs of repairs are to be covered by the leaseholder (應為landlord).
我沒有意識到洩漏問題。不過不用擔心，您的租賃協議規定，維修費用將由承租人（應為房東）承擔。
As for the noise, the construction should wrap up in three weeks.
至於噪音，施工將在三週內完成。
Tom Bradley 14:10
湯姆·布拉德利 14:10
Three weeks is still a very long time. If possible, I'd rather just end the agreement early and look for a new apartment.
三個星期還是很長的時間。如果可以的話，我寧願早點終止協議，尋找新的公寓。
Bill Hart 14:16
比爾·哈特 14:16
I'm sorry to hear that. If you would really like to, we can end the lease. But be aware that ending the lease early forfeits your deposit.
聽到這個消息我很遺憾。如果您確實願意，我們可以終止租約。但請注意，提前終止租約會沒收您的押金。
What issue is being discussed?
正在討論什麼問題？
Renewing a rental lease for an apartment.
續簽公寓的租賃合約。
Problems a tenant has with an apartment.
租戶對公寓的問題。
Who should cover the cost of installing a bath.
誰應該承擔安裝浴缸的費用。
An unruly neighbor disturbing a tenant.
不守規矩的鄰居打擾了房客。
At 14:16, what does Bill Hart mean when he says "But be aware that ending the lease early forfeits your deposit."?
14:16，比爾·哈特 (Bill Hart) 說“但請注意，提前終止租約將沒收您的押金”，這是什麼意思？
Tom will lose some money ending the lease early.
提前結束租約湯姆會損失一些錢。
Tom will need to deposit extra money to leave.
湯姆需要存額外的錢才能離開。
Tom will have to give up any money he won.
湯姆將不得不放棄他贏得的所有錢。
Tom cannot end the lease agreement early.
湯姆不能提前終止租約。